export const data = [
    {
      question: "What is the Sun's primary function?",
      option1: "Provide light",
      option2: "Generate heat",
      option3: "Give warmth",
      option4: "All of the above",
      ans: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "What makes Mercury extremely hot during the day?",
      option1: "Thick clouds",
      option2: "Lack of air",
      option3: "Proximity to the Sun",
      option4: "Presence of moons",
      ans: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Why is Venus often called Earth's sister planet?",
      option1: "Similar size",
      option2: "Similar distance from Sun",
      option3: "Similar atmospheric composition",
      option4: "Similar number of moons",
      ans: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "What special feature does Earth possess regarding its distance from the Sun?",
      option1: "Close proximity",
      option2: "Optimal distance",
      option3: "Constant heat",
      option4: "Unusual temperature",
      ans: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Why is Mars referred to as the 'Red Planet'?",
      option1: "Presence of deserts",
      option2: "Color of its surface",
      option3: "Abundance of moons",
      option4: "Lack of atmosphere",
      ans: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "What distinguishes Jupiter in the night sky without a telescope?",
      option1: "Red spot",
      option2: "Giant size",
      option3: "Colorful stripes",
      option4: "Brightness",
      ans: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "What is Saturn famous for in our solar system?",
      option1: "Thick clouds",
      option2: "Rocky surface",
      option3: "Beautiful rings",
      option4: "Strong winds",
      ans: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "How does Uranus differ from other planets in terms of rotation?",
      option1: "Upright spin",
      option2: "No rotation",
      option3: "Sideways spin",
      option4: "Rapid rotation",
      ans: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "What distinguishes Neptune's appearance?",
      option1: "Red color",
      option2: "Deep blue color",
      option3: "Yellow color",
      option4: "Green color",
      ans: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "What is notable about Neptune's moons?",
      option1: "Large size",
      option2: "Many storms",
      option3: "Strong winds",
      option4: "Mysterious nature",
      ans: 4,
    },
  ];
  